一名35岁至40岁的女性
One female in her late thirties
和3名未成年人
and three minors.
多处刺伤及钝器击伤
Multiple stab wounds and blunt-force trauma.
她前夫有嫌疑吗
What about the ex-husband?
法院说他太太申请了对他的限制令
Court said the wife had a restraining order against him.
狄伦·伯奈特  他那天晚上
Dylan Bennet. He spent the night
喝了瓶杰克·丹尼
with a bottle of Jack Daniel's.
那是他离婚后的第一个圣诞
It was his first Christmas without his family.
还有其他证据吗
All the more reason.
你是没看到他来认领家人时的样子
Well, you didn't see him when he id-ed his family.
像被货车碾过一样
Looked like he'd been hit by a freight train.
看到他的孩子这个样  到处是血
Seeing his kids like that. All the blood.
对他而言绝对是恶梦
Yeah, it was definitely a nightmare for him.
要真是他干的
If this guy did it,
他都能获奥斯卡奖了
he gets my vote for a goddamn Academy Award.
我们假设是他们的继父
Let's say the stepfather,
格雷迪·爱德华干的
this Grady Edwards did it.
-我们知道他什么  -什么都不知道
- What do we got on him? - Nothing.
听说他是从堪萨斯州来的
Said he was from Kansas.
但我们在数据库里找不到匹配的人
Except we can't find a match in any database.
而且他停订了报纸  这让他有时间人间蒸发
And he stopped the newspaper to have time to disappear.
我们觉得他以前可能做过同样的案子
And we think he might have done this before.
3年前  在新泽西
Three years ago in New Jersey,
一个妻子和3个孩子
a wife and three kids.
后脑枪伤
Gunshot wounds to the back of the head.
继父同样人间蒸发
The stepfather disappeared.
他遇到被害人的时候都在租房子住
Lived in a rented room where he met the victims.
两个房东都是老妇女
Both rooms were owned by older women.
其中在新泽西的那个女人说
One of the women who lives in New Jersey said,
"他是个很好的人"
"He's a wonderful man,"
"总是及时用现金付租金"
"always paid his rent on time and in cash."
顺理成章的  她从来没要过他的证件
So, of course, she never asked him for any identification.
不  他很聪明  想想我们发现
No, he's smart. The Toyota land cruiser
他丢弃的那辆丰田陆地巡洋舰
that we found abandoned?
现金付款
Paid for in cash.
不要求登记驾照
No driver's license required for registration.
没有信用卡  什么都没有  也就是说...
No credit cards, no anything. Which means...
不需要带照片的证件
No photo id required.
永远是离婚或鳏夫身份
Always a divorced or widowed situation.
这家伙是个魔鬼
I'm telling you, this guy's a monster.
就算你说的这人是凶手
Even if this is your guy,
那也过了半年了
it's been six months.
他现在可能在任何一个地方
He could be anywhere by now.
妈妈  贝斯说我们不能拿这些
Mom, Beth says I can't get these.
肖恩  我们不要这些
Sean, we're not getting these.
你们俩不许吵了
Hey! You two stop arguing.
为什么每次都是她来挑
Why does she always get to
我们的饼干  这不公平
pick the kind of cookies we get? It's not fair!
生活就是不公平的  生活就是
Life is not fair. Life is
得由女人来挑饼干
about the woman getting to pick the cookies.
不好意思  他们有时候不太听话
Sorry, they get a little out of control sometimes.
小孩子嘛
They're just kids.
不过你越快明白这个饼干的问题
But the sooner you figure out the cookie deal,
你的生活就会越轻松
the easier your life's gonna be.
我只是说说而已
I'm just saying.
这是女人的世界  我们只是来做客的
It's a woman's world and we're just guests here.
聪明人  看来你妻子很幸运
Wise man. I'd say your wife is very lucky.
我已经没妻子了
I'm not married anymore.
我还戴着它  但是去年在一场车祸中
I still wear it, but I lost
我的妻子和女儿都去世了
my wife and daughter in an accident last year.
-酒后驾驶  -天啊  真抱歉
- Drunk driver. - God, I'm so sorry.
没事
It's okay.
-能帮个忙吗  -当然
- I could use a little help, though. - Sure.
花生酱在哪儿
Where is the peanut butter?
我刚搬来波特兰  还不太熟悉这家店
I just moved to Portland and I don't know this store yet.
-往那边两列货架  -那边?  谢谢
- It's actually two aisles over. - This way? Thank you.
不用客气
You're so welcome.
记得我跟你说的话哦
Remember what I told you.
怎么了
What?
如果我不知道的话
If I didn't know better,
我一定会以为你在跟踪我
I'd think you were following me.
我通常没这么开放
I'm not usually this forward,
但我最近离了婚  而且...
but I'm recently divorced and...
我正要带孩子们去吃批萨
I'm taking my kids for pizza,
你要不要一起去
so I thought maybe you might want to go.
-批萨?  -实际上是我
- Pizza? - The truth is,
太想跟成年人聊聊天了
I'm just dying for some adult conversation.
我通常不是这样轻浮的
Well, I'm not usually this easy.
大卫·哈里斯
David Harris.
苏珊  苏珊·哈丁
Susan. Susan Harding.
-很高兴认识你  -我也是
- It's very nice to meet you. - It's nice to meet you.
半年后
我还是不相信她没来机场
I still can't believe she didn't come to the airport.
我跟你说了  她有事
I told you, she had some things to do.
-帮帮忙  -好的
- A little help here. - Yeah.
至少还有我啊
At least you have me.
你看到过那个家伙吗
So, have you met this guy?
看到过  我来看你妈妈的时候
Yeah, a couple of times. You know,
遇到过他几次
when I came by to say hi to your Mom.
他挺好的
He seems cool.
但她貌似圣诞节之后才认识他的吧
Okay, but she's only known him since,
这也太快了
What, like, after Christmas? That's so fast.
得了  给他个机会
Well...Come on, give it a chance.
不要做傻事
You know? Before you do something stupid.
-什么傻事  -我也不知道
- Like what? - I don't know. Like,
比如惹你老妈生气
irritating your Mom
让她把你送回军事学校
and getting sent back to military school.
我只是说她这事做得太着急了
I'm just saying, it seems
你不觉得吗
like she's rushing into things. Don't you think?
我觉得怎么安排她的生活
I think it's her business
是她自己的事
what she does with her personal life.
而她最大的可能就是毁掉它
And she tends to screw that up, mostly.
得啦  迈克尔  振作一点
Come on, Michael, chill on this one,
求你了  别跟你妈妈吵架了
please? No fights with your Mom.
-好吧  -好的  我有样东西给你看
- Okay. - Okay. I got something to show you.
惊讶吧
Surprise!
太惊讶了  真是让人惊讶  谢谢
Well, this is a surprise. This is a surprise. Thank you.
很高兴你回家了
I'm so happy to have you home.
迈克尔  过得怎么样
Hey, Michael. What's up?
肖恩  天啊
Hey. Sean. Holy crap,
-你这么大了  -谢谢
- You're huge. - Thanks.
过来  我想你
I missed you. Come here.
贝斯  我也想你
Beth. I missed you, too.
-欢迎回家  -杰姬阿姨
- Welcome home. - Hey, Aunt Jackie.
-莉亚  -亲爱的
- Leah, hey. - Hi, sweetie.
让我看看  你头发长长了
Let me look at you. Your hair's gotten longer.
是的  一年后他们就会要求剪短
Yeah. They ease up on you after a year.
你看上去真像大人
You look so...so much like a man.
我还以为是小男孩呢
I was expecting a boy.
这就是部队的作用
That's what the military does.
打造男人  强壮的好男人
Builds men. Good, strong men.
迈克尔  这是大卫
Michael, this is David.
大卫  这是迈克尔
David, Michael.
-这是标准发型吗  -不
- Is that a regulation cut? - No.
它并不是真正的军队
It wasn't real military.
只是个差生学校
It was just a school for screwups.
很高兴终于见到你了
Well, good to finally meet you.
我听说过很多关于你的事
I've heard so much about you.
一切好像都很好
Everything seems to be going great.
肖恩和贝斯爱他
Sean and Beth love him.
怎么会不爱呢
What's not to love?
他好得不像是真的
Yeah, he's almost too good to be true.
别提这个话题  杰姬
Don't start, Jackie.
我开玩笑的  开玩笑的  我喜欢他
I'm kidding. I'm kidding. I like him.
你觉不觉得我跟一个才认识半年的
Do you think I'm crazy to be
男人订婚太疯狂了?
engaged to someone I've only known for six months?
你一直都很疯狂  跟他没关系
You've always been crazy. That has nothing to do with him.
他貌似也有点疯狂  为你而狂
He seems a little crazy, too, about you.
-大家都吃饱了吗  -饱了...
- Everyone have enough to eat? - Yeah...
我想来个求婚致词
I would like to propose a toast.
首先  我想谢谢苏珊  肖恩和贝斯
First of all, I want to thank Susan and Sean and Beth,
他们在很短的时间接纳了我
Who, in a very short time,
让我有家的感觉
have taken me in and made me feel at home.
这个...这对我来说真是美梦成真
This is...it's a dream come true for me.
谢谢
Thank you.
也谢谢迈克尔
And to Michael.
你回来让家完整了
Your return makes us complete.
家是最重要的东西
Family is the most important thing.
没有它  我们就一无所有
Without it, we have nothing.
-欢迎回来  迈克尔  -好啊  好啊
- Welcome home, Michael. - Hear, hear.
好啊  好啊  迈克尔
Hear, hear, Michael.
这下子搞得我想吐了
I think I'm a little nauseous after that.
别这样
Stop it.
你想要点喝的吗
You want something to drink?
不  不用  我有这个
No, no, no, I got this.
我们也有一个惊喜要给你
We have a surprise for you, too.
-真的吗  -杰姬托了些关系
- Really? - Jackie pulled a few strings
她替你找了份工作
and she can get you a job
跟她一起做房产中介
working with her as a real estate agent.
-我不行  -等一下  你当然行
- I couldn't. - Wait a minute. Of course you can.
行吧?  你跟着我  我会带你上手的
Okay? Just follow me around and I'll get you all set up.
这可是我们的好机会
It's a great opportunity
她竭尽全力才办到的
for us and she really went out of her way.
我总不能对我未来的新娘
Well, I can't say no to my bride-to-be
或者她姐姐说不  是吧
or her sister, can I?
谢谢你  杰姬
Thank you, Jackie.
别谢我  谢她
Don't thank me. Thank her.
是她说服我
Because she's the one who convinced me
让我带你入行的
to get you off the road
-这样她可以监视着你  -是吗
- So she can keep an eye on you. - Did you?
谢谢  我去跟你儿子聊聊
Thank you. I'm gonna go have a word with your son.
天啊  我希望迈克尔能接纳他
God, I hope Michael takes to him.
他会的  他只是被离婚搞懵了
He will. He's just been blindsided by the divorce.
他会缓过气来的
He'll bounce back.
迈克尔  给我几分钟
Michael. Give me four minutes.
我们在地下室里面见
Meet me in the basement.
他说什么
So, what'd he say?
他让我去地下室找他
He said he wants me to meet him in the basement.
-地下室?  -是的
- In the basement? - Yeah.
为什么
Why?
不知道  我要去找找原因了
I don't know. Well, I guess I'm about to find out.
那两个是我的  不过其他的你随便用
Those two are mine. But you're welcome to use the others.
这些是用来做什么的
What's all this for?
我自封为木匠
Well, I'm a bit of a wannabe carpenter.
我自己打造了这些储物柜
I built these storage cabinets myself.
我现在正在修补阁楼
And I'm working up in the attic
那里损坏真严重
right now on some termite damage.
我想我们需要一个真正的致词
I think we need a real toast.
男人之间的谈话
Just the guys.
这地方我专门用来藏好东西
This is where I keep the good stuff.
来了
There we go.
别让你妈妈知道我有个藏酒的柜子
Now, don't let your Mom know I've got a tequila stash.
我拼了老命才让她相信我很完美
I've worked my ass off trying to convince her I'm perfect.
我知道这很让人震惊
I know this must be a bit of a shock,
你妈妈和我要结婚了
your Mom and me getting married and all,
但是我希望你明白  我希望我们
but I want you to know, I want us
能真正成为一个家庭
to be a real family.
因为没有它  我们就一无所有?
Because without it, we have nothing?
是的  一语中的
Okay. Touch.
我有时候有些老套
So I get a little corny sometimes,
但我是认真的
but I meant what I said.
你让我来应付你妈妈
You just let me handle your mother,
我肯定能让你留在这里
and I'm gonna make sure you stay right here,
你属于这里
where you belong.
不再让你去军校了
No more military school.
我们得把这个家庭重组起来  你跟我
We're gonna put this family back together, you and me,
-父亲和儿子  -是继父
- Father and son. - Stepfather.
继父
Stepfather
和儿子
And son.
口感滑腻  是吧
That's smooth, isn't it?
你妈妈告诉我  你是个游泳健将
So your mother tells me you're one hell of a swimmer.
是的  我游得不错
Yeah, I do okay.
我以前参加过游泳比赛
You know, I used to swim in competition.
在俄勒冈大学
In college, at U of O.
第二年很重要
Your senior year is gonna be very important.
或许你能拿到哪个学校的游泳奖学金呢
You could maybe get a college scholarship swimming.
今年夏天你应该训练
You should be training this summer.
在后院的那个池子里面可很难训练起来
It's kind of hard to train in a backyard pool.
也许吧  但我听说你以前学校
Maybe. But I hear your old school
里面有个夏泳项目
has a summer swim program.
是的  但我已经不能再去那里游了
It does, but I can't use that pool anymore.
那都过去了
That's the past.
这一杯敬将来
Here is to the future.
记得吗  我明天得去看我爷爷奶奶
Remember, I have to go see my grandparents tomorrow.
是的
Yeah, that's right.
我后天回来  真抱歉
But I'll be back the day after. I'm sorry.
不  没关系  虽然我才回来
No, that's all right. I mean, it's the day I get back,
但没关系  我会叫其他人来
But that's fine. I'll call someone else.
闭嘴  我很抱歉
Shut up. I'm sorry.
听着  我想拿到驾照
Listen, I want to get my license.
你能带我去车管局吗
So, can you take me by the DMV?
-也许吧  我考虑一下  -干吗不愿意
- Maybe. I'll think about it. - Why not?
实际上我有些喜欢你依赖我
I kind of like having you dependent on me, actually.
行啊  上车吧
All right, get in the car.
-晚安  -晚安
- Good night. - Good night.
-晚安  莉亚  -再见
- Good night, Leah. - Bye.
很高兴你回来  迈克尔
Glad you're home, Michael.
谢谢  杰姬阿姨
Thanks, Aunt Jackie.
我很高兴回家了  谢谢你过来
I'm so glad to be home. Thank you for coming.
你觉得大卫说他会让你妈妈
Do you think David meant what
让你留下来  是当真的吗
he said about getting your Mom to let you stay?
他说他会做到的  我们到时候看吧
He said he was gonna make it happen, so we'll see.
再见  亲爱的
Sweet. Bye.
很辛苦的一天吧
A lot for one day, huh?
不  不...很好  谢谢
No, no, it was...it was nice. Thanks.
我努力过头了  你可以这样说
I'm trying too hard. You can say it.
迈克尔  我知道对你来说
Look, Michael, I know it's
家里有其他男人会很不爽
difficult to come home to another man in the house.
但我需要你试着与他相处  好吗
I just need you to try and get along, okay?
妈妈  以后再说教好吗
Mom, can we just hold the lectures,
求你了  我才刚到家
please? I've been home for two seconds.
好的
Okay.
他真的是个好人
He's a really good guy.
他很关心我
And he cares about me and
我们正努力开始我们的新生活
we're trying to start a new life together.
而你不希望我把这个搞砸掉
And you don't want me to mess that up.
这不公平
Well, that's not fair.
不  不  不  我明白
No, no, no, I get it. I'll
我会尽量为你和你的新生活打开方便之门
try not to inconvenience you and your new life.
-迈克尔  -对不起  我...
- Michael. - I'm sorry. I...
我太累了  妈妈
I'm pretty tired, Mom.
好的  好的
Okay. Okay.
晚安
Good night.
或许他该在那里读二年级
Maybe he should stay there his senior year.
但他应该跟他的家人一起待在这里
But his place is here with his family.
是的  可是你不知道他是怎么样的
Yeah, but you don't know what he was like.
他跟什么样的孩子一起出去鬼混
The kids he was hanging out with,
他撒谎  情绪失控
the lying. His temper was out of control.
相信我  我希望他能待在这里
Believe me, I want him here
比什么都想
more than anything in the world.
我只希望他做好了准备
I just hope he's ready.
你说得对
You're right.
你准备好了吗
Are you ready?
那得看情况了
Well, it depends.
你准备好这个了吗
Are you ready for it?
好香啊
That smells good.
-工作怎么样  -工作很好
- How was work? - Work was great.
-这个给你  -谢谢
- These are for you. - Thank you.
迈克尔
Michael.
-这是什么  -你原来学校更衣室
- What's this? - Your locker key to the boys' gym
储物柜的钥匙
at your old high school.
游泳队6月的第一个星期开始训练
The swim team starts training first week in July.
等一下  你怎么搞到这个的
Wait, how did you swing this?
我跟运动主管瑞弗太太
I had a little chat with Mrs. Rivers,
谈了一下  她真是
the athletic director,
个心胸开阔的女人
A very open-minded woman.
大卫  你太好了
David, that was so sweet.
真的  这真难以置信
Yeah, that's incredible.
目前为止还只是个试用期
It's just a probationary period for now.
这可不保证他们明年秋天会
There's no guarantee they'll let
让你回来  但我们以后再说这个
you back in the fall. But we'll work on that later.
这对我意义太重大了  太谢谢你了
It means a lot. Thank you so much.
不客气
You're welcome.
我们吃什么呢
So, what are we having here?
我觉得好酷啊
Okay, I just think it's so cool
他真的做到了他要做的事情
that he actually did what he said he was gonna do.
我知道  我知道
I know. I know.
看吧  我说所有的事都会解决的
See, I told you everything was gonna work out.
是的  也许你是对的
Yeah, maybe you're right.
我们明天还是要去车管局吧
Hey, we still going to the DMV tomorrow?
好  我大约10点左右到
Yeah. I'll be by around 10:00.
-行  听上去很不错  -好的
- Yeah, that sounds good. - All right.
-晚安  -晚安
- Good night. - Night.
肖恩  请把声音开小点
Hey, Sean, turn that down, please!
好的
Yes!
肖恩  把声音开小  我是认真的
Sean, turn that down now! I mean it!
你妈妈说把声音开小点
Your mother said to turn it down!
你觉得他们这个年纪
Do you think it's a good idea
就这样亲热好吗
they're so passionate at their age?
他们小学就认识了
They've known each other since grade school.
她对迈克尔有好影响
She's a good influence on Michael.
你别那么迂腐
You should stop being so old-fashioned.
你妈妈遇到大卫可真幸运
I think it's so lucky that your Mom met David.
为什么这么说
Why is that?
他会是你能与我一起待在这里的关键因素
He is gonna be your ticket to staying here with me.
或许我并不想与你一起待在这里呢
Maybe I don't want to stay here with you.
或许你想回到那个全是男生的军校去
Maybe you want to go back to an all-boys military school.
或许呢
Maybe.
可是我喜欢看着你
But I like looking at you.
这就是为什么我们是天生一对的原因
That's why we make a good couple.
因为我喜欢你看着我
Because I like you looking at me.
你还好吗  肖恩
You okay, Sean?
我很好
Yeah, I'm okay.
-你确定吗  兄弟  -这样真好
- You sure, buddy? - This is great.
我真怀念这样的家庭聚餐
I've missed family dinners like this.
怀念?  这是不是意味着
You've missed them? Does that mean
你以前结过婚
you were married before?
大卫在一场车祸中失去了
David lost his wife and daughter
他的妻子和女儿
in an accident.
是的  司机喝醉了
Yeah, a drunk driver.
我不知道  真对不起
I had no idea. I'm sorry,
大卫  我很抱歉
David. I'm sorry.
我想这就是为什么家庭对我
I guess that's why family is
这么重要的原因  迈克尔
so important to me, Michael.
是的  家庭很重要
Well, family is important.
我们家可没有这么好的经验
We haven't always had such great experiences as a family.
这可不全是爸爸的错
Hey, it wasn't all Dad's fault.
我没说是他的错
No, I didn't say it was.
但我们家其实也没那么糟
But, you know, our family wasn't that bad.
我在电视上看到一个女人开车
I saw on TV this woman who drove
带上3个小孩从桥上冲了下去
off a bridge with her three kids in the back seat.
小姑娘  这可不适合吃饭的时候聊
That is so not dinner-table conversation, young lady.
他们全淹死了
They all drowned.
这种事真让我费解
That kind of thing really gets to me,
居然有人能这样对自己的孩子
that someone could do that to her own children.
这真让人搞不懂  要怎么样才会让一个
It makes you wonder, though, what it takes
人做这么变态的事情啊
to make someone do something so sick.
好了  我们谈点别的吧
Okay. Can we change the conversation?
好的  对不起
Yeah, I'm sorry.
爸爸
Dad!
也许他们让她失望了
Maybe they disappointed her.
爸爸
Dad!
你们好吗  我来拿
Hey, how are you? Let me take this.
我很好  谢谢
I'm good. Thanks.
-亲爱的  -爸爸
- Hey, sweetie. - Hi, Dad.
-你不去跟他问声好吗  -不去
- Aren't you gonna say hello to him? - No.
-猎枪  -什么
- Shotgun! - What?
你不可能有猎枪的
There's no way you're getting shotgun.
孩子们  别闹了
Hey. Hey, work it out, guys. Work it out.
周日带他们回来  他们要去露营
Back on Sunday. They're going to camp.
我们还有很多事要做
We have a million things to do.
我知道他们要去露营
I know they're going to camp.
我只在城里留几天
I'm only in town a couple days.
带他们去看场开拓者的球赛
I'm taking the kids to a Blazers Game.
他们晚上可以跟我一起住在宾馆里
They can spend the night with me at the hotel.
明天我就把他们送回来
I'll have them back tomorrow.
-你那个还是学生的女朋友呢  -那都过去了
- Where's the co-ed girlfriend? - That's over.
实际上  她现在正在攻读博士
Actually, she was working for a Ph.D.
她其实不比你年轻多少
She wasn't that much younger than you were.
她只是对自己更加细心一些而已
She just took a little better care of herself, that's all.
-迈克尔回家了吗  -他不想见你
- Is Michael home? - He doesn't want to see you.
-这是他说的还是你说的  -他说的
- Those his words or yours? - His.
我说的是"你要晚了登记入住了"
"Your check is late" are mine.
只是确认一下你没有在里面花钱
Just make sure you don't spend
找人取代我
any of the money on my replacement in there.
没有必要找人取代你  杰伊  没人想念你
It's not necessary to replace you, Jay. You're not missed.
我也很高兴见到你  苏珊
Good to see you, too, Susan.
你们准备好了吗
You guys ready?
没事吧
Everything okay?
他永远都这么混蛋
He's just always such an ass.
迈克尔  杰姬让我明天下午
So, Michael, Jackie has
去一个开放销售的房屋那里看看
me covering an open house in the afternoon,
明天你和我中午一起吃个饭  怎么样
but let's you and me have lunch tomorrow. What do you say?
那太好了
That'd be really nice.
-很好  -太好了
- Yeah, that'd be good. - Great.
卡特太太  你好
Hey, Mrs. Cutter, how are you?
你好  苏珊
I'm fine, Susan.
有张通缉犯的画像...
There was a police sketch...
我可以保证那不是大卫
I can assure you it's not David.
别担心  那绝对不是他
Don't worry. It's so not him.
好吧  如果你看见了  到我这边来  我们可以聊聊
Okay. If you see it, come over and let's talk about it.
-好的  谢谢了  卡特太太  -没事
- Okay. Thanks, Mrs. Cutter. - All right.
-你还好吗  -是的
- You all right? - Yeah.
是卡特太太
That was Mrs. Cutter.
她被邻里称为"养猫老太"
She's known in the neighborhood as "The cat lady. "
带着她那一大堆猫中的一只顺道经过
Stopped by with one of her gazillion cats.
-真让我过敏  -她说什么了
- They make my allergies go crazy. - What'd she want?
她想告诉我
Wanted to tell me that she
她在美国头号通缉犯的网页上
had seen this story on America's Most Wanted
看到了一个凶手
about this killer and
那凶手的画像和你很像
that the police sketch looked just like you.
我只能憋住不在她面前笑出来
It was all I could do not to laugh in her face.
你认识艾瑞卡·哈蒙吗
You know Erica Harmon, right?
几年前
Okay, so a couple years ago,
她跟艾瑞卡·哈蒙的老公说
she tells Erica Harmon's husband
艾瑞卡有外遇
that Erica is having an affair
因为她每天早晨都看到有个男的
because she sees this man sneaking into their house
在他一离开后就溜进他们家
every morning just after he leaves.
-她真的有婚外恋吗  -是
- And was she? - Well, yeah.
那不就得了
Well, there you go, then.
可那不关她的事
Well, it wasn't any of her business
而且她在告诉他之前  跟整个邻里都说了一遍
and she told the entire neighborhood before she told him.
太棒了  这将让我成为邻里间的大人物  是吗
Great. This'll make me a hit with the neighbors, huh?
我得走了
I gotta go.
我觉得我还不如
I think I'd rather be the
那个偷溜进哈蒙太太家的神秘男人
mystery man sneaking into Mrs. Harmon's house.
-她长什么样  -别说了
- What's she look like? - Stop it.
你们在哪儿吃午餐
Hey, where are you having lunch?
我到时候要送迈克尔过去
Because I need to drop Michael off.
办公室附近有个小餐厅
There's a diner across from the office
吃完之后我会在去开放房屋的路上把他送回家
and I'll bring him home on my way to the open house.
祝你今天愉快
Have a great day.
-早上好  妈妈  -早上好  懒鬼
- Hey, Mom. - Hey, sleepyhead.
-想吃点什么吗  -嗯  谢谢
- Want something to eat? - Yes, please.
好的
Okay.
-大卫哪儿了  -你刚跟他错过
- Where's David? - You just missed him.
卡特太太  早上好
Good morning, Mrs. Cutter.
想吃甜点吗
Okay, anybody got a sweet tooth?
-想要点甜点吗  -不了
- Do you want dessert? - No, no.
-你确定吗  再来点茶  还是什么  -不了 我饱了
- You sure? Some more tea? Anything? - No. No, I'm fine.
-那好吧  买单  谢谢  -没问题
- All right. Just the check, please. - No problem.
-谢谢你请我吃饭  -不客气  那个...
- Thank you for lunch, by the way. - Absolutely. So...
我真正想跟你说的是...
What I really wanted to talk to you about was...
我需要你的帮助
Well, I need a favor.
什么帮助
Well, what kind of favor?
我想让你做我的伴郎
I'd like you to be my best man.
-我?  -如果你能答应的话  我会感到非常荣幸
- Me? - I'd really be honored if you would.
我没有更好的人选了
There's no one else I'd rather have.
我知道我有时候对家庭问题
I know sometimes I get a
变得有点激动
little carried away with the whole family thing,
但是  我真的非常高兴你回来了
but, you know, truth is, I'm really happy you're home.
而且  像我说的那样  我要确保你一直在家里住着
And like I said, I'm gonna make sure you stay home
确保这个家庭完整  好吗
and this family stays complete. Right?
-给您  -谢谢
- Here you go. - Thank you.
那么
So,
你觉得怎么样
what do you say?
我知道你妈妈会很高兴的
I know it would make your mother very happy.
好吧  好吧
Yeah. Yeah, okay.
太棒了  这太棒了
That's great. That is great!
为了不显得那么多愁善感
You know, without sounding too sentimental,
我想跟你说
I want to tell you,
那天在超市与你母亲的相遇
meeting your mother that day in the supermarket
改变了我的人生
changed my life.
一切曾经都那么冷酷无情
It was hard, you know,
在我的妻子和女儿遇害之后
after what happened to my wife and daughter.
我亲爱的米歇尔是我的全部
My little Michelle was my whole world, my whole life.
看着她成长是我生命的全部
Watching her grow up was everything.
你会明白我说的话
You'll understand what I'm talking about
等你有了自己的孩子
when you have kids of your own.
并不是说让你和凯莉仓促地做些什么
Not that you and Kelly should be rushing into anything.
好吗
Okay?
不  不  别担心
No, no, no. Don't worry.
如果你精明的话  这还有好些年呢
You got years to go if you're smart.
当那来临时  我认为你就该明白我的意思了
When it happens, I think you'll see what I mean.
他们就是全部
They're everything.
丽莎下周就11岁了
Lisa would have turned 11 next week.
-丽莎是谁  -我女儿啊
- Who's Lisa? - My daughter.
-谢谢  -不客气
- Thanks. - Pleasure.
不好意思  我以为你说她叫米歇尔
I'm sorry. I thought you said her name was Michelle.
是吗
Did I?
是丽莎-米歇尔  你肯定听错了
It's Lisa-Michelle. You must have heard it wrong.
不好意思
I'm sorry.
没事  下周就11岁了
Yeah. 11 next week.
我操
Damn it!
打扰下
Excuse me.
Excuse me!
-你们好  -我们是鲍德温一家
- Hello, there. - We're the Baldwins.
我们打电话问了关于房子的事
We called about the house.
鲍德温先生  鲍德温太太
Mrs. Baldwin. Mr. Baldwin.
很高兴见到你们  我是大卫·哈里斯
Good to meet you. I'm David Harris.
-鲍德温胎体  你有孩子吗  -3个女儿
- Mrs. Baldwin, do you have any children? - Three girls.
3个女儿?  你会喜欢这地方的
Three girls? You're gonna love this place.
美国头号通缉犯网
寻找灭门惨案失踪继父  格雷迪·爱德华
待在这儿  好好吃饭
Stay here. Finish your dinner.
我来了
Okay. I'm coming.
好了
All right. Yeah.
乖  乖  宝贝儿  乖
Come on. Come on, baby. Come on.
让我们来看看是谁
Yeah. Let's see who it is.
午夜?  午夜?
Midnight? Midnight?
午夜呢  他去哪儿了
Where is that cat? Where is he? Midnight?
那只午夜去哪儿了
Where is that Midnight?
过来  你在做什么
Come here. What are you doing?
出什么事了
What's the matter?
那你要不要
So, are you?
要什么
Am I what?
做他的伴郎
Gonna be his best man.
应该是吧  我都答应了...
Yeah. Yeah, I guess. I said yes, so...
怎么了
What?
我要有另一个父亲了
I'm about to get another father.
你要知道  我和原来那个父亲都不说话
You know, and I can't talk to the one I have now.
可能你该开始说了
Well, maybe you should start.
出什么事了
What's wrong?
-你关门了吗  -关了
- Didn't you close your door? - Yeah.
贝斯  是你吗
Beth? Is that you?
肖恩?  肖恩?
Sean? Sean?
没有人
No, there's no one here.
怎么了
What?
天哪  大卫
Jesus, David.
拜托  你要去哪儿
Hey, come on. Where you going?
-我还是回家吧  -你不用走
- I better go home. - You don't have to leave.
没事
No, it's okay.
你刚才在看我们吗
Were you just watching us?
看你们做什么  我刚下班回家
Doing what? I just got home from work.
我要洗澡准备吃晚餐
I'm gonna take a shower and get ready for dinner.
你和凯莉在一起这么长时间
You and Kelly have been together for a long time.
我要说的只是我希望你小心点
All I'm saying is, I just want you to be careful.
她看起来是个非常好的女孩
She seems like a very nice young woman.
这也就是为什么一个男孩
Which is why a young man
应当对他的感情更加谨慎
should be more discreet with his affections.
什么意思
Meaning what? What does that mean?
人们可能会误解她
People might get the wrong idea about her.
你不会想要那样的  是吗
You wouldn't want that, now, would you?
你让人们怎么看
What do you suppose people think about you
-你和我母亲一起住  -迈克尔
- moving in with my mother? - Michael.
不好意思  请你道歉
Excuse me. Apologize.
-不用  为什么  -有点不尊敬
- No. For what? - Being disrespectful.
没关系
It's okay. It's okay.
开放式的家庭谈话是好事儿  是吗
It's healthy to have open family dialogue, right?
是
Yeah.
今天怎么样
How was your day?
有点忙
It was busy.
卡特太太今天来过这儿吗
Was Mrs. Cutter here today?
没有  可能是因为我去过的房子
No. It's probably from the
那里有猫...
house I was showing. They have cats and...
肖恩  贝斯...
Sean. Beth...
如果你再敢对我孩子动手
If you ever lay a hand on one of my kids again,
你他妈就死定了
it'll be the last thing you ever do!
你说什么
What are you talking about?
这混蛋想要掐死肖恩
This bastard tried to choke Sean.
我没掐任何人
I didn't choke anybody.
肖恩说你用手圈住他的脖子  而且很疼
Sean says you put your hand around his neck and it hurt.
他妈妈跟他说让他
His mother told him to turn
把游戏声音关小点  他不听
down his video game and he wasn't listening to her.
我只是想告诉他要有点规矩
I was just trying to show him a little discipline.
从我看到的来说  这家里是少了点规矩
From what I've seen, that's lacking a bit in this family.
如果你再敢碰我的孩子
If you ever touch my family again,
-我就杀了你  我对上帝发誓  -别闹了
- I will kill you! I swear to God! - Stop it.
-拜托...  -这已经不是你的家了  杰伊
- Come on... - This is not your family anymore, Jay.
-你对这个男人都了解些什么  -停下
- What do you even know about this guy? - Stop.
-你对这个男人都了解些什么  -别闹了
- What do you know about him? - Stop it!
我知道他没跟他的秘书上床
I know he's not sleeping with his secretary!
你什么都不知道
You don't know a goddamn thing!
如果你再不走我就叫警察了
I'll call the police if you don't leave!
你什么都不知道
Not a goddamn thing!
你听到我说的了  你要是再碰我的孩子
You heard what I said. You touch my kids again,
你麻烦就大了
you got some big trouble coming.
上帝啊
Oh, my God.
对不起
I'm so sorry.
没事  过来
It's okay. Come here.
对不起
I'm so sorry.
他有什么权利
He had no goddamn right
那样抓着肖恩  凭什么
grabbing Sean like that. No goddamn right!
你以后别再这样了  拜托  冷静点
You can't do this anymore! Come on. Calm down, please.
爸爸  给
Dad, here.
你掉了这个
You dropped this.
你要走的时候  它从你口袋里掉出来了
It fell out of your pocket when you were going at it.
谢谢
Thanks.
你阻止了我在里面做蠢事
You stopped me from doing something really dumb in there.
可能吧
Yeah, I probably did.
我不喜欢这个人
I don't like this guy.
我不相信他  你了解他吗
I don't trust him. I mean, what do you know about this guy?
不比你了解的多
Not any more than you, really.
你长高了
You got taller.
你得知道  已经一年了
Yeah, well, you know, it's been a year.
等等  等等
Hey, hey, come on.
-跟我聊一会儿  好吗  -你想干什么
- Talk to me for a second, will you? - What do you want?
不知道  想和你聊聊
I don't know. I want to talk to you.
你妈妈说你不想见我
Your Mom says you don't want to see me.
是真的吗
Is that true?
我不知道  爸爸  可不是我离开家的
I don't know, Dad. You know, I'm not the one who left.
我离开了你妈妈  但我没离开你
I left your Mom. I didn't leave you.
你们这些孩子对我来说是世界上最重要的
You kids are the most important thing in the world to me.
是  你用一种有趣的方式表现了出来
Well, yeah, yeah, you have a funny way of showing that.
我知道我搞砸了
Hey, I know. I screwed up.
我感到很抱歉
I feel really bad about that,
但我想补偿你
but I'd like to make it up to you.
怎么  你以后不再见我了
What, you're not gonna see me?
以后不再跟我说话了
You're not gonna talk to me?
不
No.
肖恩  你还好吗
Are you okay, Sean?
是的
Yeah.
我想我不应该告诉爸爸
I guess I shouldn't have told Dad.
-到底什么...  -那不是你的错  肖恩
- Well, what... - No, it wasn't your fault, Sean.
我不应该那样做的  那不对
I shouldn't have done what I did. It wasn't right.
我不是你爸爸
I'm not your father.
可能以后的某天会是...
Maybe someday, but...
但这对我来说是新的  我会犯错
This is all new to me again. I'm gonna make mistakes.
我希望你可以原谅我的所作所为
And I just hope you can forgive me when I do.
可以吗
Can you do that?
我保证
I promise,
以后再也不会发生了  好吗
It'll never happen again, okay?
做朋友好吗
Friends?
-朋友  -好的
- Friends. - Yeah. All right.
我不该那样做
I shouldn't have done it.
只是我知道一个
It's just that
没有父亲的家庭
I see a family without a father
一切有多容易坍塌
and I know how easy it can all fall apart.
如果我要成为你的一部分
If I'm ever gonna be a part of you,
我需要得到他们的尊重
I need to gain their respect.
还有信任
And trust.
我不知道你是如何成长起来的
I don't know how you were raised,
大卫  但是我家不允许体罚
David, but my family never used physical force.
我不允许那样
It's not okay with me.
当然
Sure.
你是对的
You're right.
来自爸爸: 今晚很高兴见到了你
我不能...不能...不能...
I can't keep...I can't...I can't...
我得让这一切正常...
I got to make this work...
没事  没事
It's all right. It's all right.
我想告诉她我很抱歉  很抱歉
I'll tell her I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
很抱歉  只是...
I'm sorry. It's just...
谢谢
Thanks.
-大卫  -怎么了
- David. - Yes. Something wrong?
没事  一切都很好
No. No, in fact, everything's great.
你在李佛的开放房屋销售仪式上
Your enthusiasm with the buyers
对销售者的热心促成了买卖
At the Reeves' open house made the sale.
太棒了
Great.
-我们需要你填这些表  -这是什么
- We need these filled out. - What are they?
社保  工资保险  劳工退休保险
Social security, payroll insurance, workman's comp.
还需要一张附有照片的身份证明
And we need a picture ID.
人事部说他们给过你表格让你填
Personnel said that they gave you the forms to fill out,
但你没给他们
but they just never got them back.
不  我什么也没拿到过
No, no, I never got anything.
别担心  我们需要这些
Don't worry about it. We need them, though,
这样我们就不用私底下付你工钱了
so we don't have to keep paying you under the table.
-我现在就填  -太好了
- I'll get all this done right away. - Great.
那不是我喜欢做的事情  仅此而已
It just wasn't something I enjoyed doing, that's all.
我不明白
Well, I don't understand,
杰姬说你天生就是做这个的
because Jackie said you were a natural.
房地产跟我不搭
Real estate is just not me.
什么意思
Well, what does that mean?
你又要四处奔走了吗
That you want to go back on the road again?
-我不知道  让我们看看  看看  -别  等等...
- I don't know. We'll see. We'll see. - No, wait. I...
我以为你享受这家庭的快乐  我是说  这晚饭...
I thought you enjoyed family. I mean, dinners like...
我知道你多不想让我离开
I know how much you hate me being gone,
但那是我最了解的一行
but it's what I know best.
让我用你电脑查查
Let me get on your computer and look around.
也许我能找到什么
Maybe I can find something
不需要经常旅行的工作
that doesn't require much travel.
老兄  你最好小点声
Dude, you better turn it down.
你担心大卫吗
Are you worried about David?
他不会碰你的  放心  我保证
He's not gonna touch you, all right? I'll make sure.
我真没用
I'm just useless.
我现在就出门了  到时见
I'm walking out the door right now. Okay, see you.
怎么样
How's it going?
有些在尤金的活儿
Couple of things down in Eugene.
我要和杰姬还有莉亚去喝一杯
Okay, well, I'm gonna go meet
顺便筹划一下婚礼
Jackie and Leah for a drink and plan the wedding.
-你想要一起来吗  -不了
- Would you like to come? - I don't think so.
找完工作之后  我要出门一趟
When I'm done with this, I'm gonna go for a run.
好
Okay.
大卫...
David...
我不想对你的工作小题大做
I didn't mean to make such a fuss about your work and all.
我不想让你做任何你不想做的事
I don't want you to do anything you don't want to do.
我想让你和我一样开心
I want you to be as happy as I am.
玩得开心
Have fun.
-苏珊不在  -孩子们怎么样
- Susan's not here. - How about the kids?
贝斯在朋友家
Beth's at a friend's.
肖恩和迈克尔在楼上玩游戏
Sean and Michael are upstairs playing video games.
听着...
Look...
那天晚上的事情  对不起
I'm sorry about the other night.
我那天晚上太混蛋了
I made an ass out of myself.
当我和苏珊吵架的时候...
It's just when Susan and I fight...
我要去机场
I was headed to the airport.
我想和孩子们说声再见...
I wanted to say goodbye to the kids and...
我想和你道歉
Well, I'd like to apologize to you
我太神经质了
for being a jerk.
我接受你的道歉  进来跟他们道别吧
Apology accepted. Come on in and say goodbye.
迈克尔告诉我你曾效力于鸭子泳队
Hey, Michael tells me you used to swim for the Ducks?
很久以前的事了
A long time ago.
-是吗  哪一年  -92年
- Yeah? What year? - '92.
真的吗  我亲自去了俄勒冈大学
Really? I went to U of O myself.
我得接下电话  不好意思
I got to grab that. Excuse me.
当然  当然
Sure. Sure.
杰伊给我发了条信息
Jay had left a message on my cell phone
说他会顺便过去和孩子们道别
saying he was gonna stop by there to say goodbye to the kids.
-他来了没  -没有  还没
- Did he come yet? - No. Not yet.
好吧  如果他来了  你可以退让一些吗
Okay, well, if he does, will you just stay out of the way?
好的  我们一会儿见
All right. I'll see you later then.
你想听听一些有趣的事吗
Hey, you want to hear something funny?
我给校友办公室打了电话
I called the alumni office
他们告诉我  他们只有4个叫大卫·哈里斯的
and they told me they only had four guys named David Harris
在30年前毕业过
graduate in the last 30 years.
其中2个已经死了  还有一个87年毕业
And two of them are dead and one graduated in '87.
另外一个是个四季度全美最佳跑卫
And the other one was that all-American running back.
你记得他吧
You remember him?
当然啦  他比你稍微黑一点  你不觉得吗
Of course, he's a little darker than you are, wouldn't you say?
那么...
So...
这样看起来你似乎对迈克尔说了谎
It's just...it seems like you might have lied to Michael
关于大学和游泳的事
about college and swimming.
这让我现在很想知道
And now it's got me wondering
就是...你还说了什么谎
just, you know, what else you might've lied about.
听着  我告诉迈克尔  我会向你核实
Hey, look, I told Michael that I would do some checking on you
而且  说实话  我很想得到答案
and, to be honest, I'd like some answers.
你听到了吗
Hey. You hear me?
听到了
Yep.
-怎么了  -我听到有声音
- What? - I heard something.
是什么
What was it?
我不知道  没什么
I don't know. It's nothing.
我不懂  我有点困惑  因为...
I don't understand. I'm kind of confused, because...
什么
About?
买家的反馈非常好
Well, the feedback from the buyers was great.
他只是觉得  那跟他想的不太一样而已
He just felt that it wasn't what he thought it was gonna be.
他四处奔波你都没问题吗
You're okay with him on the road?
他正在试着找
He's gonna try to find something
可以不需要经常出差的工作
where he doesn't have to travel that much.
我只是希望他能开心  他快乐我就快乐
And I just want him to be happy. If he's happy, I'm happy.
你可以走了  我想拿一下他的行李
There you go. I just want to get his bags.
-打开后备箱  -你拿吧
- Pop the trunk? - You got it.
我是杰伊·哈丁  请留言
This is Jay Harding. Leave a message.
爸爸  是我
Hey, Dad. It's me.
你在哪儿  给我回电话  再见
Where are you? Call me. Bye.
大卫
David!
什么事  迈克尔
Yeah, what do you need, Michael?
没什么
Nothing.
其实在迈克尔的派对上  你问我
You know when you asked me at Michael's party
我是不是觉得你太冲动
if I thought you were rushing into things?
我现在觉得你也许是有点
I'm thinking now that maybe you are.
你对大卫到底了解多少
I mean, how much do you really know about David?
我向他要他资料的同一天
The same day that I ask him for details about his past,
他就不干了
he just up and quits.
-你不觉得奇怪吗  -不  不觉得
- You don't find that strange? - No, I don't.
你知道我想做什么吗  我想去拉斯维加斯
You know what I want to do? I want to go to Vegas
然后举办那种只要10分钟的婚礼
and have one of those 10-minute weddings.
很不错
Nice.
大卫想要在教堂结婚
David wants to have a church wedding.
很不错  什么教堂
That's great. What church? I mean,
你都不知道他信什么吧
do you even know what religion he is?
我才不在乎他信什么教
I don't care what goddamn religion he is.
好了  你都开始听起来像杰伊了
Okay, you're starting to sound just like Jay.
他指责我对大卫一无所知
He's accused me of not knowing anything about David.
你知道我知道的是什么吗
You know what I do know?
大卫对我很好
David has been good to me.
他对孩子们也很好  他们喜欢他
He's good to the kids. They love him.
他使我的生命重获意义  我...
He's made my life worth living again. I mean, I...
很久以来  第一次
For the first time in a long time,
我满怀微笑期待未来
I'm looking forward to the future with a smile.
我只希望大家会为我高兴
I just wish everybody would be happy for me.
这个要求很过分吗
Is that too much to ask?
不  一点也不
No, it's not.
就个人而言  我支持你
Personally, I'm with you. Hey,
要是可以  我要在拉斯维加斯洗牙
I'd have my teeth cleaned in Vegas if I could.
可以吧
Right?
-冲  冲  冲  小心  -我刚避开了那辆车
- Go! Go! Go! Watch it! - I just missed that car.
伙计们
Hey, guys.
-妈妈  -和杰姬还有莉亚进行得怎么样
- Hey, Mom. - How'd it go with Jackie and Leah?
我们决定该去维加斯
We decided we should go to Vegas.
-我马上就回来  -迈克尔呢
- I'll be right back. - Where's Michael?
他在他房间
He's in his room.
我觉得他很郁闷他父亲一直没有出现
I think he's a little upset that his father never showed.
这果然很杰伊
That is so typical of Jay.
-亲爱的  -什么
- Honey? - Yeah.
我有事向你忏悔
I have a confession to make.
我不小心摔坏了
I accidentally broke the
客厅的这个水晶花瓶
crystal vase that was in the living room.
没关系的
That's okay.
它是杰伊的姐姐送的结婚礼物
It was a wedding gift from Jay's sister.
反正我从来没喜欢过它
I never liked it anyway.
你不喜欢?
You didn't?
-还有她  -那我就不觉得内疚了
- Or her. - Then I don't feel so bad.
你不觉得这有点古怪吗
You don't think it's a little weird
我问他要背景资料  然后突然间
that I ask for some background information, and suddenly,
他就不想再做房地产了
he doesn't want to sell real estate anymore?
不  没必要啊
No, not necessarily.
我喜欢大卫  他是个绅士
I like David. He's a gentleman.
他总是买单  杰伊就很小气
He always picks up the tab. Jay was so cheap.
不过你知道我觉得什么奇怪吗
Do you know what I do think is weird,
他总是付现金
though? He always pays in cash.
谁不想要积分换里程
Who doesn't want the miles?
你知道吗  我从没想过我会这么说
You know, I never thought I would ever say this,
不过我觉得我要给杰伊打个电话
but I think I'm gonna give Jay a call.
如果他也不信大卫
I mean, if he's not buying this either,
那么也许就值得调查一下了
then maybe it's worth checking into.
他没有现身吗
Hey. He didn't show up?
对
No.
我很抱歉
I'm so sorry.
-没关系  -不  有关系
- That's okay. - No, it's not okay.
他从未在你需要的时候出现过
He's never been there for you
像一个父亲该做的那样
like a father should be.
而有一部分是我的错
And part of that's my fault
因为我不应该
because I never should
允许它继续了那么久
have allowed it to go on as long as it did.
所以大卫才对我如此重要
That's why David's so important to me.
因为他在乎你们
Because he cares about you kids.
他想要你在这儿  成为你生活的一部分
He wants you to be here and be part of your lives.
他也太完美了吧
He's so perfect, isn't he?
摘下来
Take those off.
我以为你可以看出大卫让我多快乐
I thought you'd be able to see how happy David makes me.
他现在是这个家的一份子
He is part of this family now.
我想要他进入我的生活
I want him in my life and
还有我们的生活  你得理解
our lives and you need to understand that.
-你明白吗  迈克尔  -是的  我明白  好了吧
- Do you understand that, Michael? - Yeah. I understand. Okay?
好吧
Okay.
-大卫  你在下面吗...  -我正在收拾东西
- David, are you down... - I'm just putting some things away.
-马上就上去  -好
- I'll be right up. - Okay.
对不起  我没能来
Sorry I didn't make it.
下次一定
Definitely next time.
不过我查了你未来继父
But I did check out your soon-to-be stepfather.
我还是不喜欢他
I still don't like him,
但至少他看起来和他说的一样
but at least he seems to be who he says he is.
能见到你很高兴  迈克尔  爸爸
It was good seeing you, Michael. Dad.
罗伯特  那儿怎么了
Hey, Robert. What happened over there?
卡特太太死了  发生了意外
Mrs. Cutter died. She had an accident.
我猜她侄女打了好几通电话
I guess her niece called a couple of times.
却一直得不到回音
Didn't hear anything from her.
所以今早她顺道过来  却发现她的尸体
So she stopped by the house and found her just this morning.
-这太杯具了  -希望你过得愉快  再见
- That's sad. - Have a good one.
妈妈  对面停了好多警车
Mom? There's a bunch of police cars across the street.
发生了什么事
What's going on?
住在对面的那个老太太
The old woman across the street?
她从楼梯上摔下来了
She fell down her stairs
摔断了脖子   养猫的那个
and broke her neck. The one with the cats.
-卡特太太?  -是的
- Mrs. Cutter? - Yeah.
太可怕了  什么时候发生的
That's horrible. When did it happen?
邮递员说她侄女今早发现她的
The mailman said her niece found her this morning.
她好可怜
That poor woman.
肖恩  快点  我们得走了  宝贝
Sean. Hurry. We got to go, honey.
我说她的那些话  实在是太愧疚了
All those things I've said about her. I feel terrible.
这可真让人心碎
It breaks my heart.
别忘了从牙医那里接他们回来  好吗
Will you remember to pick them up from the dentist? OK?
-好  我会的  再见了  孩子们  -再见
- Yeah, I will. Okay, guys. - Bye.
-一会儿见  -一会儿见
- See you. - I'll see you.
-你好  -大卫  我是杰姬
- Hello. - David, it's Jackie.
你好  杰姬  有事吗
Hey, Jackie. What's up?
我打来是为了提醒你那些表格
I'm just calling to remind you about those forms.
-我已经不在那儿工作了  -我知道
- I'm not working there anymore. - I know.
只是我们还是需要州和联邦的纳税通知单
It's just, we still need the state and federal tax papers
而且我明天就走
and I'm leaving tomorrow.
我要飞去夏威夷两星期和莉亚见面
I'm catching a flight to meet Leah in Hawaii for two weeks,
所以我很想在走之前把文件都整理好
and so I'd really like to get that paperwork in before I leave.
我今天很忙
I'm a bit crunched for time today.
我一会儿还要从牙医那里把孩子们接回来...
I have to pick the kids up from the dentist later...
只需要几分钟就好
It'll only take a few minutes.
-我尽量吧  -谢...
- I'll see what I can do. - Thanks...
卡特太太的事太让人难过了  不是吗
It's really too bad what happened to Mrs. Cutter, isn't it?
人有旦夕祸福
Accidents happen.
是她大限已到罢了
It just must have been her time.
大学申请书
College applications.
我的辅导员说我们应该
My adviser said we should
早点申请  免得我们进不了俄勒冈大学
file early in case we don't get into U of O.
好吧
Okay.
-快来  -来啦
- Come on. - I'm coming.
听起来充其量都是些捕风捉影
It all sounds circumstantial at best to me.
我知道  我知道是的
I know, I know it does. I know it does.
但是我跟你说  这真的让我心里发毛了
But I'm telling you, it's really starting to give me the creeps.
你仔细想想  拜托
Just think about it, please.
一天  这个女人告诉我妈妈她看的这个节目
One day, this woman tells my Mom about this show that she saw,
第二天  她就死了  她现在死了
and the next, she's dead. She's dead now.
这是个意外  你自己说的
It was an accident. You said so yourself.
那他是怎么知道的
So how does he know that
她从楼梯上滚下来摔断了脖子
she broke her neck falling down the stairs?
他怎么会知道
How does he know that?
邮递员根本只字未提
The mailman never said anything about that.
他们说的话我全听到了  我发誓
I heard the whole conversation, I swear.
我要是能告诉我妈就好了
I wish I could tell my Mom about this.
如果跟你妈妈提这件事
If you bring this up to your Mom,
她会把你送回去的
she's gonna send you back.
你必须承认  他在餐桌上对
Hey, you got to admit, the comment at the dinner table
杀了自己骨肉的那个女人的评论很不寻常
about the woman who killed her kids was kind of weird.
拜托  我毫不夸张地说这很奇怪
Come on, it was weird to say the least.
还有他女儿
And then his daughter.
怎么可能有人搞不清自己女儿的名字
How do you mix up your daughter's name like that?
他没有  她的名字叫丽莎-米歇尔
He didn't. Her name was Lisa-Michelle.
你说是他说的
That's what you said he said.
-我是说了  但你不在那儿  -是啊
- I said he said that. But you weren't there. - Right?
你没有看到他的表情  都写在他的脸上了
You didn't see his face. It's in his face.
我就直说吧
Let me get this straight, all right?
-那个古怪的邻居...  -是的
- The neighborhood weirdo... - Yeah.
看了一部关于一个男人屠杀了全家的节目
...sees a show about a man who kills his family
然后你觉得那个大卫
and then you think that David
混淆了自己女儿的名字
mixed up the name of his daughter,
因此他就是那个杀了他全家的家伙
So therefore he's the guy that killed his family?
-我不知道  -是啊  我就是这么理解的
- I don't know. - Yeah, that all adds up to me.
听着  你说过你父亲调查过他了  对吧
Look, you said your Dad checked up on him, right?
-而且什么问题都没有  -是的
- And everything was cool. - Yeah.
那么好了  对吧
Okay, then. Right?
什么事也没有  放轻松
It's fine. Relax.
我们不先把这个做完吗
Are we gonna finish these?
宝贝  拜托
Babe, come on.
该死  迈克尔
Damn it, Michael.
迈克尔
Michael.
你在钻牛角尖
You're obsessing.
你知道吗  你只是有点
You know, you're just a little
受不了你妈妈嫁给一个陌生人罢了
freaked out that your Mom's marrying a stranger.
我妈妈要嫁给杰克时我也是这样的
I was the same way when my Mom was gonna marry Jack.
后来却发现他很不错
You know? And then he turned out to be cool.
如果你一定要对什么固执
If you're gonna obsess about something,
你应该对真正有意义的事固执
you should obsess about something that really matters.
比如
Like what?
比如我
Like me.
我不想再和你异地恋了
I don't want to have another long-distance relationship with you.
所以注意重点
So keep your eye on the ball.
我要去接肖恩和贝斯  一小时后回来
I'm gonna pick up Sean and Beth. I'll be back in an hour.
-你们俩没问题吧  -没有  会有什么问题
- Will you two be all right? - Yeah, why wouldn't we be?
一会儿见  规矩点
I'll see you in a while then. Behave.
走
Come on.
-你要干什么  -我想翻一下他的东西
- What are you gonna do? - I'm just gonna look through his stuff.
你疯了
You're crazy.
-你会后悔的  -除非我被抓住了
- You're so gonna regret doing this. - Only if I get caught.
迈克尔  拜托  我不想这么做
Michael, come on, I don't want to do this.
听着  如果我们什么也没找到
Look, if we find nothing,
我就再也不提了  我保证
I'll drop it forever. I promise.
我刚买完东西
I just finished shopping,
所以还是我去接孩子吧
so I'm gonna pick the kids up after all.
我刚离开家  已经在路上了
I just left the house. I'm on my way.
不用了  我就快到了
That's okay 'cause I'm so much closer.
-不过还是谢谢  -那好吧
- But thank you. - Well, okay then.
-家里见  再见  -好  再见
- I'll see you at home. Bye. - Okay. Bye.
你刚听到了没
Did you just hear that?
没有  这儿只有我们  凯莉  没关系
No. We're alone, Kelly. It's fine.
天啊  天啊  该死
Oh, my God. Oh, my God. Shit!
操
Shit!
迈克尔
Michael.
迈克尔  你在里面吗
Michael, you in there?
你在这里吗  迈克尔
You in here, Michael?
迈克尔
Michael!
迈克尔  你爸爸后来有联络你吗
Michael, did you ever hear from your Dad?
我收到一条他发的短信...
Well, I got a text message from him, so...
真的?  他说了什么
Really? What'd he say?
只是说他感到很抱歉  没有在起飞前过来
Just that he was sorry for not coming by before his flight.
我试着打了几个电话
I've tried calling a couple
但只接通了语音留言  所以...
times and I just get his voicemail, so...
我不知道  我可能今晚会给他发短信吧
I don't know. I'll probably text him tonight.
亲爱的  他肯定是
Honey, I'm sure he just
工作太忙了  你也知道你爸
got crazy with work. You know how Dad gets.
对  没事  我知道
Yeah, yeah. No, I know.
大卫?
David?
大卫  你没事吧
David, you okay?
我很好
Yes, I'm fine.
我知道  我差点尿裤子  我吓死了
I know. I almost pissed my pants, I was so scared.
那可不会让我冲动  顺便说一句
You know, that's not a turn-on, by the way.
迈克尔  闭嘴  我是认真的
Michael, shut up. I'm being serious.
-我知道  我知道  -真的?
- I know. I know. - You do?
是的  我一直在
Yeah. I mean, I've been thinking
考虑你说的话  所有的事情  真的
about what you said, about all of it, really.
然后我决定...
And I've decided that...
你是对的  我是说也许  也许
That you're right. I mean, maybe, maybe,
我是在钻牛角尖了
I am obsessing.
-你真这么想?  -我爸爸说没事  所以...
- You think? - I mean, my Dad said he was all right, so...
我想我只是因为不习惯而已
I guess the rest of it is just me freaking out.
我觉得你该明天来
I think you should come by tomorrow
我们填完那些大学申请表
and we'll get these college applications finished.
-不再钻牛角尖了?  -对  我对天发誓
- No more obsessing? - No, no, no, I swear on my life.
-好吧  那么明天见  -好  晚安
- All right? So I'll see you tomorrow. - Okay. Good night.
好  晚安
Okay. Night.
进来吧
Yeah, come in.
-有时间吧  -当然  怎么了
- Hey, you got a sec? - Sure. What's up?
-你好吗  -不错
- How you doing? - Fine.
也许我误会了  不过一度
Maybe I'm wrong, but for a while there,
我以为我们有个好的开始
I thought we were off to a good start.
而现在我开始觉得
And now I'm getting the
我们有点不投缘
feeling that somehow we're not on the same page.
我知道不可能一蹴而就  迈克尔
I know it can't happen overnight, Michael.
但为了这个家
But for the sake of the family,
你必须明白这里要有所改变了
you gotta understand that things are going to change around here.
不会像以前一样
It's not gonna be like it was,
但希望可以更好
but hopefully better.
-对  我明白  我知道  -很好
- Yeah, I do. I know. - Good.
我只是希望你可以对我光明磊落
I just want you to always be up-front with me.
不要说谎  不要偷偷摸摸的
No lies, no sneaking around.
你妈妈不会喜欢你这样的
Your Mom wouldn't like that.
你需要赢回她对你的信任
And you need to win back her trust.
我不想看到你不得不再回到那个学校去了
I don't want to see you have to go back to that school again.
-你对天发誓了的  -就看看警方的素描
- You swore on your life. - Just look at the police sketches.
求你了  我别无他求
Please, that's all I'm asking.
他们确实神似  你得承认
There is a resemblance. You got to admit,
这个有点像他
it kind of looks like him.
你知道这个其实像谁吗
You know who this actually looks like?
他看起来像洛克威尔先生
It looks like Mr. Rockwell,
我们高中一年级的生物老师
our biology teacher from freshman year.
才不  你根本没认真看
No, you hardly looked at it.
好吧  他可以是任何人
All right. It could be anybody.
听着  这是格雷迪·爱德华
Look, this is Grady Edwards.
警方无法确认他的身份
The police couldn't match his ID.
他们没有发现任何指纹  而且不谋而合的是
They couldn't trace any fingerprints. And there are similarities.
也说他做过销售  也说他经常出差
He said he was in sales. He said he traveled a lot.
他们也从没有发现任何他的照片
They can never find any pictures of him either,
所以我今早问了贝斯
so I asked Beth this morning
她能不能在家里找到大卫的照片
if she could find any pictures of him in the house,
随便什么照片都行
any pictures of David.
结果什么也没有  他根本就不拍照
There aren't any because he doesn't like having his picture taken, apparently.
那又怎样  我也不喜欢
So what? Neither do I.
但我发誓我没有杀那个女人和她的孩子
But I swear I didn't kill that woman and her kids. Okay?
这什么也证明不了
It doesn't prove anything.
历史记录里有这个网站
The website was in the browser history.
-他肯定看过  -那又怎样
- He was checking it out. - So what if he was?
也有可能是你妈妈
Or maybe it was your Mom.
或者是他们两个人
Or maybe they both were
都是听了卡特夫人的话好奇看的
because they were curious about what Mrs. Cutter said.
你不是也因此看过了吗
I mean, that's what made you check it out.
好吧
All right.
没什么了  当我没说
It's fine. Just forget about it.
-我们还要填完这些东西吗  迈克尔  -等等吧
- Are we gonna finish these, Michael? - Hold on one second.
怎么了  你不想再和我上同一所大学了?
What is it? You just don't want to go to college with me anymore?
顺便说下  我和马克·霍福德有一腿
By the way, I'm screwing Mark Helford.
你说什么
What?
我要走了  回家了
I'm leaving. I'm going home.
晚点打给我  不然后果你知道的
Call me later. Or, you know what,
还是别打了  我不在乎
don't actually. I don't care. Whatever. You know.
凯莉  凯莉  别这样
Kelly. Kelly, come on.
对不起  我不知道你在这里
I'm sorry. God, I didn't even know you were there.
你吓了我一大跳  哈里斯先生
You scared me, Mr. Harris.
叫我大卫就行
Call me David.
我只是来喝点柠檬汽水的  来点吗
I was just getting myself a lemonade. Do you want one?
不用了  谢谢
No, that's okay.
你和迈克尔看起来好像闹矛盾了
Looked like Michael and you were having a bit of a fight.
没有
No.
真的没什么
It's nothing, really.
要我帮忙吗
Anything I can help you with?
-不用了  没事  -真的?
- No, it's cool. - You sure?
他好像有什么心事
Something seems to be troubling him.
或许我们两能帮他走出困惑
Maybe the two of us can help him work it out.
我也不知道  或许只是...
I don't know. It's just...
我不明白  他最近很混蛋
I don't get it. He's been such a jerk lately.
这才叫男人  我们都是混蛋
It's called being a guy. We're all jerks.
所以女人才喜欢
That's why you women like us.
我们就像你们的研究课题
We're like projects you take on.
听着  凯莉
See, Kelly,
你这样的女孩成熟得很快
Young women like you seem to mature faster.
而男孩要更长时间才能赶上
It takes boys a little longer to catch up.
也许哪天你会成为哈丁家的一员
You know, you might be a part of the Harding family one day.
我也希望你能把我看成家人
And I'd like you to think of me as you would the others, as family, too.
我会的
Yeah, I do.
那是肯定的
I mean, you know, I will.
有什么需要帮忙
And if you ever need anything,
来找我好了
please come to me.
尤其是关于迈克尔的
Especially if it concerns Michael.
我们谁也不想看到他做傻事  对吧
Neither of us want to see him do something stupid, do we?
做出那些要让他回军校的事情
Something that might get him sent back to military school.
他不会的
He won't.
但是谢谢你  哈里斯先生
But thank you, Mr. Harris.
大卫  叫我大卫就行
David. Call me David.
我现在不在  有事请留言
Hi. I'm not here, I'm there. Leave a message.
是我
Hey, it's me.
我晚上非常想见你  给我电话  再见
I really want to see you tonight, so give me a call. Bye.
很抱歉这么长时间才回复你
Sorry it took so long to get back.
过几天我打给你
I'll try to call you in the next few days.
希望你一切都好  爸爸
Hope all is well. Dad.
我一直在试着打你电话
I've tried to reach you on your phone.
想和你谈谈关于大卫的事
Want to talk to you about David.
给我电话  杰姬
Call me. Jackie.
我是杰伊·哈丁  请留言
This is Jay Harding. Leave a message.
我还要再考虑下再给你电话
I have to call you back on that,
但是报酬听起来还能接受
but the money sounds like we're in the ballpark.
明天再谈  好的
We'll talk tomorrow. All right.
怎么了  迈克尔  你看起来像撞鬼了
What's up, Michael? You look like you've seen a ghost.
没有  我...
No, I...
我听到电话响了
I heard a phone ring.
我以为是地下室的声音
I thought it sounded like it was coming from the basement.
是我的电话
You probably just heard mine.
我就要有工作了
I got a call on a job. I think I'm gonna take it.
报酬还不错  还不用经常出差
Money sounds good. I won't have to travel much.
钥匙在哪儿  大卫  地下室的钥匙呢
Hey, where's the key? David, where's the key to the basement?
我刚才还在想
Yeah, I was wondering that myself.
我要下去找些工具  可钥匙不见了
I needed to get some of my tools this morning. The key was gone.
或许有人拿了忘记放回去
Someone took it out and forgot to put it back.
忘了放回什么
Forgot to put what back?
-亲爱的  -伙计们
- Hey, honey. - Hey, guys.
地下室的钥匙不见了
That key to the lock on the basement door is missing.
明天早上我来叫个锁匠
I'll call a locksmith in the morning.
或者
Better yet,
我去商场买把新锁来换
I'll go down to home depot and get a replacement.
这把都旧了
That lock was getting old.
我自己就能弄好的  顺便说下
I can do the work myself. By the way,
我找到工作了
I think I found a job.
太棒了
That's fantastic.
是的  报酬很好而且出差少
Yeah, the pay's good and very little travel.
-我喜欢  -就知道你会的
- I like that. - I thought you would.
-让我们来庆祝一下  -好的
- Let's celebrate. - Okay.
-你这个暑假该找份工作  -他都已经有了
- Maybe you should get a job this summer. - He's already got one.
他是这个泳池的救生员
He's the lifeguard at the pool here.
不  我是认真的
No, no, I'm serious.
这样你就能攒钱买车了
That way you could earn money toward getting a car.
你领到驾照了
You're getting your license.
需要一辆自己的车
You're gonna need a car of your own.
尤其是你要在波特兰读高三的话
Especially if you're gonna spend your senior year here in Portland.
-等等  妈妈  -你是认真的吗
- Wait, Mom. - Are you serious?
-你是说真的?  -是的  我想大卫是对的
- Wait, do you mean that? - Yeah, I think David's right.
只有你在  我们才是一个完整的家庭
The only way for us to be a proper family is if you're home with us.
况且你上了大学  就不会回家了
Besides, when you go to college, you're not going to come back.
-谁要甜点  -我要
- Who wants dessert? - Me. I do.
我想把肖恩和贝斯送到卡根家里去
I'm gonna drop Sean and Beth off at the Kagan's,
让他们在那里过夜
cause they're gonna spend the night
卡利的妈妈明天会送他们去野营
and then Carrie's Mom's gonna drive them up to camp tomorrow.
-想一起来吗  -我很想去
- Want to ride with me? - I wish I could.
但我要上网去把这个工作定下来
But I need to get back on the internet and finalize this job.
用不了几个小时
Okay. I should only be a couple hours.
就几个小时  好的
A couple hours. Okay.
-玩得开心  -再见
- Well, have fun, guys. - Bye.
-再见  -再见  大卫
- Bye. - Bye, David.
-苏珊  -怎么了
- Susan. - Yeah.
我爱你
I love you.
我也爱你
I love you, too.
你晚上有什么计划
What are your plans this evening?
我可能要去见凯莉
I might go see Kelly.
要多久
For how long?
还不确定  怎么了
I don't know. Why?
当心点  新闻说风暴雨要来了
Just be careful. The news said there's a big storm headed this way.
没有了
It's gone.
-什么东西  -我以前拍过的他的照片
- What? - The shot I took of him before?
没有了  都被他删了
It's gone. He deleted it
现在一张他的照片也没有了
and now there's no pictures of him anywhere.
-或许是你不小心删的  -不会的...
- Well, maybe you deleted it by accident. - No, I didn't...
你没听见我说吗
Have you not been listening to me?
我想你说过他没有看到你拍
I thought you said he didn't see you take it.
或许他看到了
Maybe he did or maybe he's been
或许他看了我的手机  我也不知道
checking my phone this whole time. I don't know.
我洗澡的时候他来我房间的
But he came into my room when I was in the shower.
他删的  我知道是他干的
He deleted it. I know he did.
他不想拍这些照片
He doesn't want his picture taken.
但这并不能说明他就是凶手
That doesn't mean he's a killer.
地下室的钥匙并没有丢
The key to the basement didn't just get lost, all right.
他一直在下面
He's always down there.
他在遮掩着什么
He's hiding something.
天气怎样  我正在收拾行李
So what's the weather like? I'm trying to pack.
你只需要比基尼和微笑
All you're gonna need is a bikini and a smile.
但你只要记得带上比基尼
Neither if you forget the bikini,
因为我的微笑就够我们俩用了
because I'll have enough smile for both of us.
-等会儿  -你在打电话?
- Hold on a sec. - Are you on your cell phone?
我是苏珊  请留言...
Hey. This is Susan. Leave me a message...
如果你还有事情没忙完  先放放吧
If you're trying to do some last-minute business, give it a rest.
你还有3个小时就要上飞机了
You've got a plane to catch in three hours.
不是的  我在找苏珊
No, I'm trying to reach Susan.
我想我干了件蠢事
I think I did something stupid.
我给杰伊打了电话
I called Jay
我还留言让他调查大卫的背景
and I left a message that I wanted him to do a background check on David.
你也知道这很愚蠢了?
You think you did something stupid?
我打给大卫关于w-2s的事情  他挂了我电话
Listen, I called him about the W-2s and he hung up on me.
他从来没有兑现过他说的
He never did anything he said that he would.
她会杀了你的
She is going to kill you.
我知道  所以我才要在杰伊之前找到她
I know. That's why I need to reach her before Jay gets to her first. Okay?
所以  帮帮我吧
So, please, do me a favor.
等我到洛杉矶转机的时候再打给你  好吗
I will call you during my layover in L.A., okay?
不用了  我今晚要去环游小岛的聚会
No, don't. I'm going on a party cruise around the island tonight.
-真的?  -快来吧
- Really? - Just get here!
我尽量
I'm trying.
-爱你  -同样爱你  再见
- Love you. - Love you, too. Bye.
在我离开之前联系不上你
I wasn't able to get you on your cell phone before I left,
但我想告诉你
but I wanted you to know
我曾让杰伊调查大卫的背景
that I left a message for Jay to run a background check on David.
至今仍没有消息
And I haven't heard back,
因此我会在到达机场后
so I'm gonna call this investigator we use at the office
打电话给我们办公室的调查员
when I get to the airport.
在你生气之前我想告诉你
Before you go ballistic, let me tell you
他拒绝向我提供任何身份或是工资证明
that he refuses to give any identification for insurance and payroll.
而且还向我撒了谎  肯定有什么隐情
And he lied to me. There's something not right here.
还有20分钟我就要去机场了
I'm leaving for the airport in about 20 minutes.
如果你没什么说的  等我回来打给你
If we don't talk, I'll call when I get back.
我爱你  不要生气
I love you. Don't be mad, please.
波特兰论坛报
Portland Tribune.
你好  我要取消订阅的报纸
Hello. I need to speak to someone about canceling a subscription.
上帝  你吓到我了  还以为家里没人
God, you scared me. I didn't think anybody was home.
-你提前回来了  -对  你去跑步了?
- You're home early. - What, did you go running?
-我要让我的头脑清醒一下  -杰姬打来电话了吗
- I needed to clear my head. - Did Jackie call?
我在家时没有
Not since I've been home.
我有一个未接来电不过她没有留言
Because I had a missed call and she didn't leave a message.
我试着联系她  可是联系不到
I tried to reach her. I couldn't.
-迈克尔呢  -一直在凯莉那里
- Where's Michael? - Over at Kelly's.
我要赶紧去换身衣服
I'm gonna change clothes real quick.
上帝  我讨厌这样的鬼天气
God, I hate it when it storms like this.
在这样电闪雷鸣的天里我总是睡不着
I can never sleep with all this thunder and lightning.
给  吃片这个
Here. Take one of these.
-这是什么  -轻度安眠药
- What is it? - It's a mild sleeping pill.
-第二天会没精神的  -睡不着也会这样
- They make you so groggy the next day. - So will no sleep.
半片就好
Just take half.
-是吗  -当然
- Really? - Sure.
我不喜欢迈克尔在这样的天出去
I don't like Michael out in this.
那打给他让他回家
Well, let's call him and get him home.
没关系的  我已经不把他当小孩子看了
No, that's okay. I've just got to stop treating him like a child.
好了  待在这里  如果你看到任何动静
All right, stay here. If you see any movement
有人上楼或者下楼
upstairs or see anyone come downstairs,
或者任何灯光  打给我  我调震动了
any lights, call me. I've got it on vibrate.
迈克尔  你要干吗
Well, Michael, what are you doing?
我要去看看那些储藏柜里到底有什么
I'm gonna find out what's in those storage cabinets.
你疯了  迈克尔  真的不行
That's insane, Michael. Really,
要是...你妈妈刚答应你留下来
What if...your Mom just told you you could stay.
如果被她知道了怎么办
What do you think's gonna happen when she finds out about this?
她会发现的...
And she will find out about it...
凯莉  他就在附近躲着  我知道的
Kelly, he's hiding something in there, all right? I know he is.
你要相信我
But you have to trust me.
求你了
Please. Please.
-自己当心  -我会的
- Just please be careful. - I will. Okay.
妈的
Shit.
在哪儿
Where is it?
亲爱的?
Honey?
总算找到了
Finally.
上帝
God.
该死的
Shit!
迈克尔  快接啊
Michael! Come on!
快啊  快啊
Come on. Come on.
快接电话  迈克尔
Pick up, Michael.
该死的
Shit!
迈克尔
Michael!
凯莉  你在干吗
What are you doing, Kelly?
凯莉
Kelly!
快啊
Come on!
凯莉
Kelly!
凯莉  凯莉
Kelly! Kelly!
凯莉
Kelly!
什么声音
What's all the noise?
我以为我能搞定的  但是不行
I thought I could make this work. But I can't!
这不是我适合的家庭
This isn't the right family for me.
你儿子是问题的关键  他太不懂尊重了
The boy is a problem. He has no respect.
你对他不够严厉
You haven't been hard enough on him.
你必须让他知道
You've got to make a boy understand!
必要的时候好好教训他
You've got to break him if necessary!
-你太软弱了  -你在说什么
- You're too weak to do that. - What are you talking about?
我本以为能行的  但还是不行
I thought it could work, but it can't!
我以为你能成为格雷迪·爱德华太太  但你不能
I thought you could be Mrs. Grady Edwards! But you can't!
-你说什么  -等等  等等
- What did you say? - Wait. Wait a minute.
我叫什么
Who am I here?
-大卫  你...  -大卫
- David, what are... - David!
大卫·哈里斯
David Harris.
妈妈
Mom!
不要  不要
No! No!
不
No!
妈妈
Mom!
凯莉  凯莉
Kelly! Kelly!
能站起来吗
Can you stand?
很好
That's it.
-迈克尔  -听我说
- Michael! - Listen to me.
妈妈  是我  是我  上帝啊
Mom, it's me. It's me. God!
他切断了所有的电话线
Among other things, he ripped out all the phones.
-我本来能杀了他的  -我们快走
- I might have killed him. - We have to go.
迈克尔  我不会让你们走的
I can't let you do that, Michael.
后退  后退  快上楼  快  快
Get back, get back. Get upstairs now! Move! Move!
-快  快啊  -滚开
- Go! Go! Go! - Stay away!
救命  救命
Help us! Help! Help!
小心你脚下
Careful where you step.
一些坏的地板我还没换呢
There's still some rotted boards I haven't replaced yet.
迈克尔  迈克尔
Michael! Michael!
-不  不  -迈克尔
- No! No! - Michael!
迈克尔
Michael!
离他远点
Get away from him!
来啊  过来啊
Come here! Come on!
别碰他
Leave him alone!
凯莉
Kelly!
-凯莉  当心  -凯莉
- Kelly, watch out! - Kelly!
来啊  来抓我啊  凯莉  快跑  妈妈
Come on, take me! Kelly! Run! Mom!
发生了什么
What happened?
你昏迷了
You were in a coma.
多久了
How long?
已经有一个月了
Just over a month.
迈克尔
Michael!
大卫呢
What about David?
他在哪儿
Where is he?
没人知道
Nobody knows.
警察来的时候他已经跑了
By the time the police got there, he was gone.
他跑了?
He's gone?
跑了?
Gone?
女士  有什么能为您效劳
Hi. Yes, Ma'am. Can I help you?
我要夜灯的小灯泡
I have got this little lightbulb that I need for their nightlights.
-能告诉我哪里能找到吗  -来吧
- Can you tell me where I can find that? - Come on!
当然  第二过道  不用客气
Yep. Aisle two. You're welcome.
安迪  罗斯  你们去哪里
Andy, Ross, where'd you go?
孩子们
Guys?
快过来  别闹了  快过来
Hey, hey, guys, come on! Knock it off! Get back over here!
快点  等等我
Come on, guys, wait for me.
很抱歉  快过来  孩子们  我们走
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry. Guys, come on. Let's go.
没事的  男孩总是喜欢捣蛋
That's okay. You know what they say, boys will be boys.
你有孩子吗
Do you have any children?
我妻子和女儿因车祸死了
I lost my wife and daughter in a car accident.
-很抱歉  -不  没关系
- I'm sorry. - No, that's okay.
已经有一年了
It's been nearly a year now.
我能体会到你的感受
I kind of know what you're going through.
我丈夫两年前也死了
I lost my husband two years ago.
我知道很难  但现在好多了
I know it's hard sometimes, but it does get easier.
但愿如此
I hope so.
我叫克里斯·埃蒙斯
Hey, I'm Chris Ames.
我叫朱莉·金  幸会
I'm Julie King. Nice to meet you.
很高兴认识你
Well, it's nice to meet you.